(Amy:)Um...
(Penny:)Did you seriously
just say, "Um"?
(Leonard:)Look, you know I love you,
(Leonard:)but you're... you're drunk
and sad and feeling lost--
Okay, so you don't
want to marry me?!
(Leonard:)-That is not what I said.
-No, forget it! I take it back!
-Offer's off the table!
-Who's in the mood to laugh?!
(Leonard:)Really not a good time.
(Sheldon:)But I used science
to construct the perfect joke.
(Penny:)-I'm gonna go.
-Penny, don't.
(Penny:)No, no, I just need to be alone.
(Sheldon:)So, a sandwich, a rabbi
and yo mama walk into a bar.
(Sheldon:)-Where are you going?
-To my room.
(Sheldon:)-Should I follow you?
-No.
(Sheldon:)-Leonard, wait.
-What?
(Sheldon:)I forgot to tell you
the sandwich is promiscuous.